I have a theory about this so let's let's go to this guy this also means grooming standards
no more beards long hair superficial individual expression we're going to cut our hair
shave our shave our beards and adhere to standards but when it so there's a whole thing about
razor bumps being an issue right and for black soldiers allow please talk more about this yeah
well when i was in black soldiers they they have certain conditions where they got bumps and it's
and when you shave it it can cut that increase and cause infection irritation so you get a medical
profile for that um and that was just understood it was an understood thing yeah i mean this is
obviously most likely a dog whistle they're insinuating that they're gonna you know ethnically
cleanse the u.s military it's probably a dog whistle that he's doing obviously the soldiers they want to
get in are gonna be your white supremacist types that's probably what this is it's also to appeal
to your white supremacist groups and get the most you know uh radical ss division type of dudes um
signing up with the military um again i don't think it's gonna work because of for a few ironic reasons
even even your most racist white supremacist neo-nazi dudes i don't think it's gonna work
why i'll tell you why because on the far right you got two factions you got your maga right who are
like your they're your trump loyalist and then you got your groipers your nick fuentes loyalists who
while they're white supremacists they're white nationalists they hate israel and they hate the
u.s government because they see the u.s government as being being loyal to israel so that's a problem for
the trump administration if they're trying to get white supremacists joining the military because
even the white supremacists hate the u.s government and hate the u.s military apparatus because they
just see it as an extension of israel so that's the problem they have on their hands and it's kind
of hilarious to see the right fragment like this because i feel like the past 50 years or 70 years
we've seen nothing but the left fragment it's nice to see the right fragment for once and i i find
it very entertaining to be quite honest what radicalized you oh you mean oh palestine when i
was 18 i i was i was a i was a christian nationalist a republican when i was in high school um where'd you
go to high school like what state doug way it was a military base doug way proving ground w doug way
proving ground is a secret military base in utah in the desert they call it area 52 that's what they call
it and it had like 250 people in my height in the whole school but um i was um i was in the desert
and i wanted to go to go to israel and join the israelis and study at hebrew university and all
that so i asked my parents hey can i go to hebrew university and study hebrew and join the idf and
all that good stuff uh i went to evangelical churches as a kid and they would definitely
um and no well and not in utah but in kansas city so in kansas city is where i got evangelicalized
i guess you can call it um and became like an evangelical zionist so when i went to um when i went
to hebrew university in jerusalem uh they happened to assign me to a dorm floor that was full of
palestinian muslims and first night i started arguing with these palestinian dudes who were on my
dorm floor and we were yelling and cussing at each other and i was unloading all my islamophobia that
i was taught in church and then after just arguing and having a great time with them i kind of felt
the brotherhood forming and that was my first night in jerusalem my first day in israel proper and i just
fell in love with them and they became my brothers and i ended up going and visiting their villages and
their families and i love the culture i love the bravery the code of honor it really spoke to my
redneck cowboy side of my family that's big on like small community codes of honor you know you're
shaking somebody's hand that's your word of honor that kind of thing and the palestinians lived like
that the israelis however were like just weird to me i'm like damn these people are just something's
wrong with them like they're they have no roots there's no deep deep like constitution within them
they all feel isolated they all feel psychologically they have issues they have this they're very racist
which i wasn't raised that way i mean like i had a lot of problematic like nationalist christian views
but i wasn't racist that was a no-no in my family but the israelis how can you be a nationalist and not
racist well like in the christian in the church world like you got your like uh thinking about think
about like your international diverse evangelical churches like your assemblies of gods you have
you know you have diversity there and everything but um it's very nationalist in the sense that it's
like america is the christian nation and the american version of christianity is the ultimate one
but the rest of the world is like you know they're they're the enemies of god or they're they're not as
advanced as christianity so my godmother is africa is african she's from zimbabwe so i was raised
yeah i was co-parented by by africans growing up since i was little so my mom was from zimbabwe
my godfather's from zimbabwe my god sibling so i grew up with them and they were part of that um
that uh that christian community as well so when i went to israel and i saw like the blatant racism
that israelis just espoused every day like i remember them saying when they saw me hug one of
my um palestinian friends at the hebrew university this girl who i was flirting with this israeli girl
she was like like you know them and i'm like yeah i know them and she's like but they're arab
and i'm like um well this is the middle east you know uh and she's like well they're bad and i'm like
and i'm like what do you mean they're bad like are you joking with me like is that i mean you you
exaggerating like no you're oh you're serious oh wow i need to talk to your parents like this is
like so she it was just every day how israelis to them racism is is not anything there's no
stigma to it it's it's just it's acceptable it's a way of life yeah yeah and they're just it wasn't
what i thought it was because i was taught that the israelis were like the the children of god they
were the ancient israelites which i've which i kind of like later on detected like no these guys are not
the ancient israelites like they're just europeans they're just europeans that just showed up like
that there's nothing uh indigenous about them so the palestinians i just fell in love with their
culture and i i basically uh they formulated who i became like i 18 years old is a very impressionable
age especially for a young white dude i could have gone down any path as a young white man like
we're we tend to be very vulnerable with what happens to us psychologically and luckily for me um
palestinians were the ones that kind of formulated my personality at a young age like i just
wanted to be like them like i wanted to be i wanted to live up to that standard of having
that code of honor and bravery so yeah but that radicalized me uh early on i became an anarchist
after that i went from republican to anarchist when i was in palestine like i was i was just like i i saw
the way the palestinians lived they lived the way that they lived they don't need a government like if
if if palestine didn't have any government like no judges no governors no police officers no military
they would be just fine because the way that they govern themselves with the with purely a code of
honor and tradition like i that convinced me that that mankind does not need government if we do it
right if we live like palestinians we wouldn't even need a government so i became an anarchist right away
i see what you're saying yeah yes if we had code you know like a cultural code you don't need
governance well that's and but i mean conceptually that's essentially what communism is supposed
to be to lead to yeah yeah absolutely you know that that's the that's what communism is supposed to
be i mean then you know it ends up getting thrown off but um right speaking because we
are the war department godspeed i've never walked into a room so silent before and if you want to
applaud you applaud you can do the fact that trump had to come in and do crowd control but like for
silence like you guys can clap if you feel like it uh it's great to see i love it it shows where the
wind's blowing in the military the look the this would have he probably would have been met with
applause if we hadn't witnessed what we witnessed in the past two years our us military brass look as
problematic as they are i'm sure they have a lot of issues going on like i'm sure they have a lot of
problems morally but they are patriots meaning they know what nation they want to prioritize and they know
they do care about the health of this country regardless of whether they're dissolute they're
they have an illusion about what the u.s government like the u.s government legacy is it doesn't matter
they're patriots and they're seeing us burn our own people you know burn our own economy destroy the
working class they're patriots they don't want that and they see us being loyal for the interest of a
foreign country that's genocidal yeah you can't expect people like that to be applauding and and
feel any type of loyalty to trump or biden you know i i think they're disillusioned in general i think
that they i think these generals watch podcasts like this i really do they're not stupid they follow
you know intellectual discourse and they do study so i'm sure we're having an effect on them in some way
shape or form so i you know that's that's what trump is trying to do he's trying to purge the u.s
military of patriots you know he's trying to get rid of them all and get nationalists the u.s military
well this is a great way to do it